	* 06/04/2024 13:43:53 - Information - Selectable update IIS-ApplicationDevelopment of package IIS-WebServer-Core-Package was successfully turned off.
	* 06/04/2024 13:43:53 - Information - Selectable update IIS-StaticContent of package IIS-WebServer-Core-Package was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:43:53 - Information - Selectable update IIS-HttpCompressionStatic of package IIS-WebServer-Core-Package was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:43:53 - Information - Selectable update IIS-ManagementConsole of package IIS-WebServer-Core-Package was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:43:53 - Information - Selectable update IIS-HttpLogging of package IIS-WebServer-Core-Package was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:43:53 - Information - Selectable update IIS-HttpErrors of package IIS-WebServer-Core-Package was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:43:53 - Information - Selectable update IIS-RequestFiltering of package IIS-WebServer-Core-Package was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:43:53 - Information - Selectable update IIS-DirectoryBrowsing of package IIS-WebServer-Core-Package was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:43:53 - Information - Selectable update IIS-DefaultDocument of package IIS-WebServer-Core-Package was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:43:53 - Information - Selectable update IIS-WebServerRole of package IIS-WebServer-Core-Package was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:43:37 - Information - Initiating changes to turn off update IIS-ApplicationDevelopment of package IIS-WebServer-Core-Package. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:43:37 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update IIS-StaticContent of package IIS-WebServer-Core-Package. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:43:37 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update IIS-HttpCompressionStatic of package IIS-WebServer-Core-Package. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:43:37 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update IIS-ManagementConsole of package IIS-WebServer-Core-Package. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:43:37 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update IIS-HttpLogging of package IIS-WebServer-Core-Package. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:43:37 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update IIS-HttpErrors of package IIS-WebServer-Core-Package. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:43:37 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update IIS-RequestFiltering of package IIS-WebServer-Core-Package. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:43:37 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update IIS-DirectoryBrowsing of package IIS-WebServer-Core-Package. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:43:37 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update IIS-DefaultDocument of package IIS-WebServer-Core-Package. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:43:37 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update IIS-WebServerRole of package IIS-WebServer-Core-Package. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:39:23 - Information - Selectable update DHCPServer of package DhcpServerRole was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:39:23 - Information - Selectable update DHCPServer-Tools of package DhcpServerToolsRole was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:39:15 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update DHCPServer of package DhcpServerRole. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:39:15 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update DHCPServer-Tools of package DhcpServerToolsRole. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:36:13 - Information - Selectable update File-Services of package FileServer-Core was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:36:11 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update File-Services of package FileServer-Core. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:33:48 - Information - Selectable update DNS-Server-Tools of package DNS-Server-Tools-Package was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:33:48 - Information - Selectable update DNS-Server-Full-Role of package DNS-Server-Full-Role-Package was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:33:44 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update DNS-Server-Tools of package DNS-Server-Tools-Package. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:33:44 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update DNS-Server-Full-Role of package DNS-Server-Full-Role-Package. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:29:18 - Information - Selectable update DirectoryServices-AdministrativeCenter of package DirectoryServices-AdministrativeCenter-Package was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:29:18 - Information - Selectable update Microsoft-Windows-GroupPolicy-ServerAdminTools-Update of package GroupPolicy-ServerTools was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:29:18 - Information - Selectable update DirectoryServices-DomainController of package DirectoryServices-DomainController-SrvFnd-Package was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:29:18 - Information - Selectable update ActiveDirectory-PowerShell of package ActiveDirectory-PowerShell-Package was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:29:18 - Information - Selectable update DirectoryServices-DomainController-Tools of package DirectoryServices-DomainController-Tools-Package was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:29:18 - Information - Selectable update RSAT-ADDS-Tools-Feature of package DirectoryServices-DomainController-Tools-Package was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:29:18 - Information - Selectable update RSAT-AD-Tools-Feature of package DirectoryServices-DomainController-Tools-Package was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:29:18 - Information - Selectable update ServerManager-Core-RSAT-Role-Tools of package ServerManager-Core-Package was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:29:18 - Information - Selectable update ServerManager-Core-RSAT of package ServerManager-Core-Package was successfully turned on.
	* 06/04/2024 13:29:04 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update DirectoryServices-AdministrativeCenter of package DirectoryServices-AdministrativeCenter-Package. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:29:04 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update Microsoft-Windows-GroupPolicy-ServerAdminTools-Update of package GroupPolicy-ServerTools. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:29:04 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update DirectoryServices-DomainController of package DirectoryServices-DomainController-SrvFnd-Package. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:29:04 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update ActiveDirectory-PowerShell of package ActiveDirectory-PowerShell-Package. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:29:04 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update DirectoryServices-DomainController-Tools of package DirectoryServices-DomainController-Tools-Package. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:29:04 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update RSAT-ADDS-Tools-Feature of package DirectoryServices-DomainController-Tools-Package. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:29:04 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update RSAT-AD-Tools-Feature of package DirectoryServices-DomainController-Tools-Package. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:29:04 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update ServerManager-Core-RSAT-Role-Tools of package ServerManager-Core-Package. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
	* 06/04/2024 13:29:04 - Information - Initiating changes to turn on update ServerManager-Core-RSAT of package ServerManager-Core-Package. Client id: DISM Package Manager Provider.
